Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Fortunoff Video Archive for Holocaust Testimonies records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1944–2017; Accession 2018-A-0014
  - Financial and administrative files
    - Financial files
      - Reports, fiscal year 2010, 2009–2010 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Endowment, fiscal year 2010, 2009–2010 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Provost office, fiscal year 2010, 2009–2010 (Box 18, Folder 30-32)
      - Library endowment, fiscal year 2011, 2010–2011 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Library current use, fiscal year 2011, 2010–2011 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
      - Provost office, fiscal year 2011, 2010–2011 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Library current use, fiscal year 2012, 2011–2012 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
      - Library endowment, fiscal year 2012, 2011–2012 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Account holder reports, fiscal year 2013, 2012–2013 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
      - Conference on Jewish Material Claims against Germany reports, 2011–2013 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Library endowment, fiscal year 2013, 2012–2013 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Library current use, fiscal year 2014, 2013–2014 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Library endowment, fiscal year 2014, 2013–2014 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Receipts, 2008–2015 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Administrative files
      - Affiliation and deposit agreement, 1984–1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Annual reports to the library, 1984–1996 (Box 19, Folder 18-20)
      - Howard Rubinstein Associates, 1997–1998 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Internal communications and minutes, 1982–1991 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Production projects, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - State of Connecticut citation honoring the Fortunoff Video Archive, Circa 1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - State of Connecticut citation honoring the tenth anniversary of Fortunoff, 1992 December 4 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Training materials
      - Interviewer names, 1983–1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Interviewer refresher course, 1990–1993 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Interviewer Training, 1983–1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Interviewer training re-interview project, 1986–1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Student training materials, Circa 1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Photographs
      - Planning group, Lanzman event, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Researchers at Fortunoff, Undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Tenth anniversary celebration, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Holocaust and apartheid, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Guide to the Holocaust Video Testimonies, Volume 1, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Stockton University, opening of the Holocaust Resource Center, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Joanne W. Rudolf, Circa 1990 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Athens Project, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Fondation Auschwitz, Circa 1990-circa 1995 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Twentieth anniversary conference, Beinecke Library, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - Twentieth anniversary conference, Sunday dinner, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Twentieth anniversary conference, L&B room reception, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Twentieth anniversary conference, Sunday morning, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - Rudolf and others viewing testimonies, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - Elie Wiesel, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 35-36)
      - Fondation Auschwitz, conference, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - Bratislava, Circa 1990-circa 1995 (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Exhibits, Circa 1990-circa 1995 (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Filming of testimonies, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - Fortunoff offices, 198? (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - Proof sheet, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 42)
      - Fortunoff Video Archive, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - Hartman, Rudof, and Liberman, Circa 1980-circa 1989 (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - Tenth anniversary exhibition, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 45)
      - Reception in Beinecke, Circa 1992 (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - Holocaust memorial preliminary sketch, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Grants
    - Conference on Jewish Material Claims against Germany
      - Digitization, 2010–2011 (Box 20, Folder 48)
      - Hebrew cataloging, 2001–2009 (Box 20, Folder 49-53)
    - Mellon/Shoah
      - Mellon Grant Proposal, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 56)
      - Shoah Foundation, background, 2002–2003 (Box 20, Folder 57)
      - Shoah Foundation training guide, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities
      - General, 2001–2002 (Box 20, Folder 59)
      - Documentation, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 60)
      - Letters of support, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 61)
      - LSF retrievals, 2003–2004 (Box 20, Folder 62)
      - Media Matters, 2003–2005 (Box 20, Folder 63)
      - Media Matters SAMMA training, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 64)
      - Report requirements, 2002–2005 (Box 20, Folder 65)
      - SAMMA, 2004–2006 (Box 20, Folder 66)
      - Vendor proposals, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Stifting Denkmal fur die Ermordeten Juden Europa (Box 20)
      - General, 2004–2009 (Box 20, Folder 68-70)
      - Contracts, 2004–2009 (Box 20, Folder 71)
      - Equipment, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 72)
      - XML Project, 2003–2004 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Holocaust Education/Prejudice Reduction Program
    - Workshop, 1988 May 4, 1988–1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Year end evaluation, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - New Haven, 1989–1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Teacher Workshop 1/10/89, Holocaust Education Prejudice Reduction Program, 1988–1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Holocaust Education Prejudice Reduction Program-Video orders, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Holocaust Education Prejudice Reduction Program-Video acquisitions, 1989–1994 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - Holocaust Education Prejudice Reduction Program '91-'93, 1991–1993 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
    - Eyewitness to History-Summer 1992, student trip (Box 21, Folder 10-12)
    - Eyewitness to History-educational materials, 1992–1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - October 1993 Workshop (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Activities, 1994–1995 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Activities, 1996–1997 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Activities, 1995–1998 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Activities, 1998–1999 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Activities, 1995–1999 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Activities, 1999–2000 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Lead Teachers, 1999–2000 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Activities, 2000–2001 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Activities, 2001–2002 (Box 21, Folder 23-24)
    - Advisory Council, 2000–2001 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Lead Teacher's Readings, 2000–2001 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Activities, 2002–2003 (Box 21, Folder 27-28)
    - Activities, 2004–2005 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Activities, 2005–2006 (Box 21, Folder 30-32)
    - Activities, 2006–2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Activities, 2007–2008 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Activities, 2008–2009 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Board, 2008–2009 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Seminar reading material, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Activities, 2009–2010 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
    - Holocaust Education Prejudice Reduction Program, 2010–2011 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Publicity and promotional materials
    - Holocaust Survivors Film Project
      - New Haven Area, 1979–1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Early Materials, 1979–1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Stationery, Circa 1979-circa 1981 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Publicity outside of New Haven, 1979–1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - 1980 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - 1981 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
    - Press Clippings, 1981–1988 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
    - Pre-Opening Publicity, 1982 November (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Establishment of the Archive, 1980–1982 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration, 1982 November 15 (Box 22, Folder 20-21)
    - Post-Inaugural Publicity, 1982 November (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - 1st Anniversary Presentation, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - 1984–1985 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - 1986–1987 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - 1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - 1990 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - 1991 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - 1992 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - 1994 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - 1995 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - 1996 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Pamphlets, Circa 1990-circa 2007 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Newsletters, 1985–2003 (Box 22, Folder 34-35)
    - Film- "Those Who Were There", 1982–1983 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Conference Programs, 1981–2012 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Related Articles, 1981–1990 (Box 22a, Folder 1-3)
    - Related Articles, 1981–1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter 2003- Proofs, Spring (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Second International Conference, 1995–1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Video Archive/ HSFP Donors & July 2013 Fund Drive, 1981–1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1982–1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Releases and pre-interviews forms
    - Releases
      - Templates, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Aa- Al, 1980–2006 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Am- Az, 1979–2008 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Ba- Be, 1979–2011 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Bf- Bo, 1980–2008 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Bp- Bz, 1979–2013 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - C, 1980–2013 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - D, 1980–2013 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - E, 1980–2004 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Fa- Fl, 1979–2015 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Fm- Fz, 1979–2014 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Ga- Gk, 1980–2017 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Gl-Go, 1979–2011 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Gp-Gz, 1979–2015 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Ha- He, 1979–2011 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Hf- Hz, 1979–2007 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - I-J, 1979–2015 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Ka-Ke, 1979–2010 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Kf-Kl, 1979–2016 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Km- Kz, 1979–2011 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - La-Leh, 1979–2016 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Lei-Lez, 1979–2010 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Lz-Lz, 1980–2014 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Ma, 1979–2016 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Mb-Me, 1980–2017 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Mf-Mz, 1980–2012 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - N-O, 1980–2014 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Pa-Pol, 1979–2013 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Plm-Q, 1984–2009 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Ra-Ri, 1980–2009 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Rj-Res, 1979–2008 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Rot-Rz, 1979–2011 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Sa-Sb, 1979–2014 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Sca-Schl, 1980–2012 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Schm-Scz, 1980–2002 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Sd-Sh, 1979–2005 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Si-Sl, 1980–2008 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Sm-Sr, 1980–2016 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Sta-Ste, 1979–2005 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Sti-Sz, 1979–2008 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - T, 1980–2005 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - U-V, 1980–2002 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Wa, 1979–2007 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - We, 1979–2014 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Wf-Y, 1980–2011 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Z, 1979–2014 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Pre-interview forms
      - A-Alt (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Alt-Az (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Baa-Bara (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - B-Bau (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Bau-Bere (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Berg-Bez (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Bf-Blan (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Blat-Blu (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Bo-Bran (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Bras-Bro (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Bri-Bz (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - C-Cle (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Cli-Z (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - D-Deb (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Dec-Dem (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Dep-Dez (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Dia-Dor (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Dot-Dz (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - E-Eli (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Ell-Ez (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - F-Fei (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Fei-Fi (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Fj-Fram (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Fran-Fe (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Fri-Fz (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Ga-Geo (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Ger-Gof (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Goj-Goz (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Gp-Gross (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Grosz-Gz (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Ha (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Heb-Herm (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Hern-Hi (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Ho-Hr (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Hu-I (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Ja-Je (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Jo-Jz (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Kaa-Kar (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Kas-Kaz (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Ke-Kim (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Kin-Kl (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Km-Korm (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Korn-Kra (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Kre-Kz (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - La (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Lea-Leh (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Lei-Leu (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Lev-Lez (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Lf-Li (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Lj-Lz (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Maa-Maq (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Mar (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Mas-Mel (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Mem-Mez (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Mf-Mi (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Mo-Mul (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Mum-Mz (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Na-Ne (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Ni-Nz (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - O (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - P-Pep (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Per-Pl (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Po-Pra (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Pre-Pz (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Q-Ra (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Re-Rj (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Rk-Ror (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Ros (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Rot-Rz (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - S-Sam (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - San-Saz (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Scha-Schl (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Schm-Schu (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Schw-Schz (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Sd-Sg (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Sh-Si (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Sj-Sn (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - So (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Sp-Std (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Ste (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Stf-Stz (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Su-Sz (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - T-Tiz (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Tom-Uz (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Vaa-Vam (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Van-Vaz (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Ve-Vz (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - W-War (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Was-Waz (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Wb-Weim (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Wein-Weis (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Weit-Wez (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Wf-Wi (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Wj-Wz (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - X-Za (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Zb-Zz (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Witness: Voices of the Holocaust
    - Contracts, 1999–2000 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - United Learning version of videorecording, 1999; 1.0 (Box 47)
    - Teacher guides and handouts, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Releases, 1979–1999 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Survivor correspondence, 1997–2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Free Press, 1998–1999 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Screening comments, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Broadcast information, 1997–2000 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Connecticut Public Television, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Internal correspondence, 1997–2000 (Box 29, Folder 24-25)
    - Book proposal, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Festivals and screenings, 1999–2000 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Poster, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Press summary, 1999–2000 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Promo, 1998–2000 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Press, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Press, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Visuals
      - General, 1997–2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - To be Filed, Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Visuals in Book
        - Visuals in Book, Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 29)
        - Sample Printings- Book, Circa 1999 (Box 30, Folder 30)
        - Arnold C., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 31)
        - Chaim E., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 32)
        - Renee H., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 34)
        - Celia K., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 35)
        - Helen K., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 36)
        - Joseph K., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 37)
        - Perla L., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 38)
        - Christa M., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 39)
        - Jay M., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 40)
        - Abraham P., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 41)
        - Edith P., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 42)
        - Werner R., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 43)
        - Frank S., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 44)
        - Robert S., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 45)
        - Martin S., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 46)
        - Joseph W., Circa 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 47-48)
  - Researcher forms and cataloging work forms
    - Loans
      - Loan forms, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Long term, 1986–2011 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Inter Library long term loans, 1996–2017 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - ILL- Contracts, 1995–1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Long term, Birkbeck College Library, 2016 February 8 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Jewish Historical Society- Hartford, 2013–2014 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Long term ILL- University of Saskatchewan, 2016 October–2016 November (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Long term, Ukrainian Center for Holocaust Studies, 2011 November–2011 December (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Long term, Halbmayr, B- Vienna, 2009–2010 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Long term, Institut d'Histoire, 2015 September–2015 October (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Long term, Loyola Notre Dame, 2012 November (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Long term, Kennesaw State Uni ILL, 2016 August–2016 September (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - ILL- National Library of Israel, 2016 September–2016 October (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - ILL- UCLA, 2016 April–2016 June (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - ILL- University of Arkansas, 2015 September–2015 October (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Long term, Lerch, B. Uni. Regensburg, 2011 December–2013 March (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Long term, Open Uni. Library, 2015 July (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Long term, Uppsala University, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Long term, von Harder, Burkhard, 2011 December (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Long term, Archive der KZ Gedenkstatte Mauthausen Fusselberger, Isolde, 2012 June–2012 July (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Long term, Yad Vashem, 2016 March (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Videotapes on loan, 1983–2014 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - 2004–2011 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - ILL University of Southampton, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Videotapes returned (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - New Haven, videotapes returned, 1988–1990 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - US Holocaust Memorial Museum/ Duplicating Project, 1989–1994 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - Harvard/ C. Christo, 1989–1990 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - New Haven, 1992–2004 (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - New Haven- general, Undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - New Haven- returned, 1990–2014 (Box 31, Folder 33-34)
      - Videotapes returned A-DE, 1983–2008 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Videotapes returned Df-Hol, 1983–2007 (Box 31, Folder 36-37)
      - Videotapes returned Hom- K, 1983–2002 (Box 31, Folder 38-39)
      - Videotapes returned- L, 1985–2007 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Videotapes returned, M-Ros, 1983–2007 (Box 31, Folder 41-42)
      - Videotapes returned, Rot-S, 1983–2008 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
      - Videotapes returned, T-Z, 1983–2008 (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
    - Registration forms
      - Current registration forms, 2010–2012 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Cornell University, Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Duke University, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Emory, 1997–2003 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - George Mason University, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Olin class, 2010 January (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Snyder class, 2010 January (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - St. Cloud State, 2005–2006 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - St. Cloud, 2001–2003 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - San Francisco State University, 2005–2006 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - San Francisco State University, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - University of Southampton, 2006–2007 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Registrants/users
      - A-B, 1983–2011 (Box 32, Folder 20-21)
      - C-D, 1983–2011 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - E, 1983–2010 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - F, 1984–2011 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - G, 1983–2011 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - H, 1984–2011 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - I-J, 1985–2010 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - K, 1983–2010 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - L, 1983–2011 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - M, 1984–2011 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - N-O, 1984–2010 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - P-Q, 1983–2011 (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - R, 1983–2011 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - S, 1983–2011 (Box 32, Folder 35-36)
      - T-V, 1985–2011 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - W-Z, 1984–2011 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Cataloging work records
      - HVT 1-25, 1979 July–1980 August (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - HVT 25- 50, 1979 August–1983 June (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - HVT 51-75, 1979 April–1980 November (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - HVT 76-100, 1979 April–1980 July (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - HVT 101-25, 1979 August–1981 August (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - HVT 126- 150, 1979 December–1989 March (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - HVT 151- 175, 1979 July–1982 October (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - HVT 176- 200, 1980 February–1983 July (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - HVT 201-225, 1979 July–1983 October (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - HVT 226- 250, 1979 August–1984 March (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - HVT 251-300, 1982 June–1984 November (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - HVT 301-350, 1983 July–1998 August (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - HVT 351-400, 1983 March–1984 December (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - HVT 401-425, 1983 March–1984 October (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - HVT 426-450, 1983 March–1984 October (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - HVT 451-500, 1983 June–1985 January (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - HVT 500-550, 1983 September–1985 May (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - HVT 551- 575, 1983 October–1985 June (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - HVT 576- 600, 1984 November–1985 July (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - HVT 601- 650, 1982 August–1986 June (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - HVT 651-675, 1980 May–1986 March (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - HVT 676-700, 1985 January–1986 May (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - HVT 701-750, 1983 May–1994 October (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - HVT 751-800, 1980 May–1986 December (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - HVT 801- 850, 1986 April–1996 October (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - HVT 851-900, 1987 March–1992 June (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - HVT 901-950, 1983 February–1987 December (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - HVT 951-975, 1987 January–1988 January (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - HVT 976-1000, 1987 July–1988 May (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - HVT 1001- 1035, 1986 November–1987 December (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - HVT 1036- 1070, 1984 May–1987 October (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - HVT 1071-1100, 1984 July–1990 March (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - HVT 1101-1125, 1987 November–1991 February (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - HVT 1126-1150, 1983 November–1989 September (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - HVT 1151-1200, 1987 April–1989 May (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - HVT 1201-1250, 1987 November–1989 May (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - HVT 1251-1300, 1987 October–1996 December (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - HVT 1301-1350, 1987 December–1990 June (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - HVT 1351-1400, 1986 February–1996 December (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - HVT 1401-1450, 1984 June–1991 January (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - HVT 1451- 1500, 1988 July–1991 May (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - HVT 1501-1550, 1988 September–1991 December (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - HVT 1551-1600, 1989 September–1992 March (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - HVT 1601-1650, 1989 April–1991 October (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - HVT 1651- 1700, 1988 January–1991 November (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - HVT 1701-1750, 1990 March–1992 June (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - HVT 1751- 1800, 1990 November–1991 October (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - HVT 1801-1850, 1985 October–1997 January (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - HVT 1851-1900, 1990 November–1993 October (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - HVT 1901-1951, 1990 October–1995 August (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - HVT 1951-2000, 1990 May–1996 May (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - HVT 2001-2050, 1990 July–1993 July (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - HVT 2051-2100, 1990 May–1993 June (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - HVT 2101-2150, 1992 April–1993 October (Box 35, Folder 15)